https://www.brattleborofoodcoop.coop/privacy-policy/

MENUMENUhomesales
Co-op DealsCo-op BasicsMonthly In-Store FlyerFresh DealsTruckload SalesShareholder Appreciation Days
events
Full CalendarKids and Adult ClassesTastings and Demos
departments
Beer & WineBulk Products
Bulk Alphabetical ListingBulk List by UPC/PLUBulk List by Category
Cheese
Tour de Fromage: Travel with Cheese
Customer ServiceDairyDeli and CaféDottie’sEducation and OutreachFrozenGrocery
Bread Deliveries
Health and BeautyHousewaresMeatProduce / FloralSeafoodShareholder ServicesWellness, Housewares, and HABA
join
Shareholder Information
Working ShareholdersShareholder Assistance FundFood for All Program
BFC Board of Directors
About the Board of DirectorsUpcoming ElectionsContact the Board of Directors
Annual Meeting 2020
community
Round Up for Change!Bag A BeanBrattleboro
Local Events
Commitment to CommunityDonation Request FormProducer of the MonthSustainabilityWhoo Knew
about
Cooperative PrinciplesEnds PoliciesBrattleboro Food Co-op's HistoryWhat’s a Co-op?
careers
Job OpeningsEmployment ApplicationOur Team
shop
Order Online or by Phone-Pickup Curbside!What’s New?Gift CardsRecipesPre-order a CasePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The Brattleboro Food Co-op is dedicated to keeping personal information collected from visitors to our web site secure and private, and to meeting existing privacy standards.
This Privacy Policy Agreement governs all data collection and usage in relation to Brattleboro Food Co-op and the Brattleboro Food Co-op website.  In using brattleborofoodcoop.coop, you are consenting to the privacy policies outlined below.
Information We Collect
This website collects various types of information, such as:
Voluntarily provided information that you submit to us via online forms: this may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information, required when you make payments, donations, or complete any online form on the Brattleboro Food Co-op web site. Brattleboro Food Co-op needs this information to deliver the services you have requested.
Embedded content from other websites (e.g. videos, social media icons, interactive elements). Embedded content from other websites, such as YouTube, may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content.
Analytics tracking by Google to monitor site usage and search engine accessibility.
Server logs which automatically collect the IP address, operating system, and page visited for every request to the web site.
How We Use Your Information
Brattleboro Food Co-op may collect and make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request.
Brattleboro Food Co-op does not sell, rent or lease our user’s data to any third parties.
Brattleboro Food Co-op may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to glean what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public. This includes Google Analytics tracking.
In addition, if you click on a social media link such as Facebook, YouTube, or Instagram, your interaction with those third party web sites will be subject to tracking by the owners of those services.
Brattleboro Food Co-op may only disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Brattleboro Food Co-op and/or our website;
Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Brattleboro Food Co-op; and
Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of https://brattleborofoodcoop.coop and/or the general public.
Your Rights Over Your Data
Brattleboro Food Co-op collects some personal data via its web site as required for the completion of online forms including contact, special order, and job application forms. This information is retained for the length of time necessary to process your request and provide you with the service requested.
Online form data is generally removed from the web site on an annual basis.
If you reside in the European Union, you may request an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Children Under Age of 13
Brattleboro Food Co-op does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.
Links to Other Web Sites
In addition, if you click on a link such as Facebook, Instagram, YouTube, or other third party, your interaction with those third party web sites will be subject to tracking by the owners of those services.
Our website does contain links to other websites. Brattleboro Food Co-op does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.
Security
Brattleboro Food Co-op maintains physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.
The company uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications to provide simple and secure access and communication of all personal information. Security software is installed to protect the server and web site from unauthorized access.
With regard to online purchases through the Brattleboro Food Co-op web site, your credit card information is not stored by the Co-op but by the payment processor, currently Stripe.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
Brattleboro Food Co-op reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those changes to our website homepage at https://brattleborofoodcoop.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Brattleboro Food Co-op decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our site. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email:  webmaster@brattleborofoodcoop.coop
Telephone: 802 257 0236
Mailing Address:  2 Main St, Brattleboro, VT, 05301
Date adopted:  January 2020
News
Update on Dottie’s Closure in December
Board of Directors Meeting Minutes: November 2020
Irio (Kenyan mashed sweet potato) Recipe
2020 BFC Election Results for BOD, Bylaws and Ratification
Is the End in Sight?
Become a Co-op Shareholder All are welcome to shop the Brattleboro Food Co-op. However, we are community owned and welcome you to join as a Co-op Shareholder and invest in a locally owned business that delivers deep community impact and offers great food.
If you are a shopper who is committed to buying organic and whole foods, committed to supporting local industry and family farms, and believe in cooperative ownership, we encourage you to invest in the longevity of our store. You will reap the benefits of being a Co-op shareholder and use your voting power to direct future business decisions.
Learn more
Newsletter Sign up to receive our twice per month newsletter that includes coupons, events and sales.  Newsletter archive.
Subscribe
Search for:
The Co-op is open EVERY DAY for walk-in shopping from 9am-8pm.
Curbside Shopping Service
Call our Hotline at 802-246-2800 or Order Online.
Click for Details!
Map & Directions
